Guide to the Deane W. Malott papers, 1951-1964
Malott, Deane W. papers, 1951-1964
- Personal correspondence of Deane W. Malott while president of Cornell University
  - O Miscellaneous., 1959-63 (Box 30, Folder 44)
  - P Miscellaneous., 1955-62 (Box 30, Folder 45)
  - P Miscellaneous., 1957-62 (Box 30, Folder 46)
    Perkins, Dexter.
  - P Miscellaneous., 1954-63 (Box 30, Folder 47)
    University of Pittsburgh.
  - University of Pittsburgh., 1962-63 (Box 30, Folder 48-67)
  - R Miscellaneous., 1957-63 (Box 30, Folder 68)
  - R Miscellaneous., 1958-62 (Box 30, Folder 69)
    Rieber, Fritz C.
  - R Miscellaneous., 1956-62 (Box 30, Folder 70)
    Rockefeller, Laurance S.; Rockwell, George H.
  - R Miscellaneous., 1957-61 (Box 30, Folder 71)
  - R Miscellaneous., 1954-63 (Box 30, Folder 72)
  - S Miscellaneous., 1954-63 (Box 30, Folder 73)
  - S Miscellaneous., 1957-63 (Box 30, Folder 74)
    Senior, John L.
  - S Miscellaneous., 1954-62 (Box 30, Folder 75)
  - S Miscellaneous., 1958-62 (Box 30, Folder 76)
  - S Miscellaneous., 1956-62 (Box 30, Folder 77)
    Stephens, Thomas E.
  - S Miscellaneous., 1955-62 (Box 30, Folder 78)
  - S Miscellaneous., 1957-62 (Box 30, Folder 79)
  - S Miscellaneous., 1954-62 (Box 30, Folder 80)
  - T Miscellaneous., 1957-62 (Box 30, Folder 81)
    Talbott, John; Teagle, Walter C.
  - T Miscellaneous. Thacker, Earl M., 1961-62 (Box 30, Folder 82)
  - T Miscellaneous., 1958-62 (Box 30, Folder 83)
    Thacker, Earl M.
  - T Miscellaneous., 1961-62 (Box 30, Folder 84)
    Thrum ' s Hawa i i an Annua 1 s.
  - T Miscellaneous., 1961-63 (Box 30, Folder 85)
    Thrum's Hawaiian Annuals.
  - T Miscellaneous., 1961-62 (Box 30, Folder 86)
    Trippe, Juan T. University of Liberia; University of West Africa (Proposed).
  - T Miscellaneous., 1953-61 (Box 30, Folder 87)
  - U Miscellaneous., 1961-62 (Box 30, Folder 88)
    Upson, Maxwell M.
  - V Miscellaneous., 1959-63 (Box 30, Folder 89)
  - W Miscellaneous., 1960-62 (Box 30, Folder 90)
    Ward, J. Carl ton.
  - W Miscellaneous., 1960-63 (Box 30, Folder 91)
    Williams, Roger. Bohemian Grove.
  - W Miscellaneous. Williams, Roger., 1960-62 (Box 30, Folder 92)
  - XYZ Miscellaneous., 1954-63 (Box 30, Folder 93)
- American Foundation for the Blind., 1958 (Box 30, Folder 94)
- Report on the Cornell student Body., 1951 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Annual Report - Cornell University Library., 1957 (Box 31, Folder 2)
- Annual Report - ROTC and Dept. of Military Science and Tactics., 1957 (Box 31, Folder 3)
- Annual Report - Division of Extramural Courses, Graduate School, Placement Service, Office of the Registrar., 1957 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Annual Report - University Testing and Service Bureau, WHCU, Summer Session, Office of Deans of Men and Women, University Faculty., 1957 (Box 31, Folder 5)
- Annual Report - Dept. of Clinical and Preventive Medicine, New York State College of Agriculture, College of Architecture, College of Arts and Sciences., 1957 (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Annual Report - School of Education, Division of Extramural Courses, Graduate School of Business and Public Administration, Graduate School, New York State College of Home Economics, School of Hotel Administration., 1957 (Box 31, Folder 7)
- Annual Report - New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations, Cornell University Medical College., 1957 (Box 31, Folder 8)
- Annual Report - Division of Unclassified Students, New York State Veterinary College, Cornell University Medical College, School of Nutrition., 1957 (Box 31, Folder 9)
- Annual Report - Summer Session, Director of Admissions, Registrar, Graduate School, Extramural Courses, Vice President for Research., 1958 (Box 31, Folder 10)
- Annual Report - Dept. of Clinical and Preventive Medicine, University Faculty, New York State College of Home Economics, Veterinary Virus Research Institute, School of Education., 1958 (Box 31, Folder 11)
- Annual Report - University Placement Service, New York State College of Agriculture, Unclassified Students, Graduate School of Business and Public Administration, Cornell University Library, Vice President for Business., 1958 (Box 31, Folder 12)
- Annual Report - University Testing and Service Bureau, School of Nursing, University Publisher, Law School, College of Architecture, Cornell University Medical College, Dept. of Physical Education and Athletics, Social Science Research Center., 1958 (Box 31, Folder 13)
- Annual Report - New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations, New York State Agricultural Experiment Station, School of Hotel Administration, Vice President J. L. Zwingle, Office of Development, Alumni Office, News Bureau, College of Engineering., 1958 (Box 31, Folder 14)
- Annual Report - School of Nutrition, College of Arts and Sciences, New York State Veterinary College, ROTC., 1958 (Box 31, Folder 15)
- Annual Report - Cornell United Religious Work, Office of Admissions., 1958 (Box 31, Folder 16)
- Annual Report - Office of Admissions, Graduate School., 1959 (Box 31, Folder 17)
- Annual Report - Graduate School, Office of Admissions, Placement Service., 1959 (Box 31, Folder 18)
- Annual Report - New York State College of Agriculture, ROTC., 1959 (Box 31, Folder 19)
- Annual Report - University Publisher, Social Science Research Center, Dept. of Clinical and Preventive Medicine., 1959 (Box 31, Folder 20)
- Annual Report - University Testing and Service Bureau, New York State College of Home Economics., 1959 (Box 31, Folder 21)
- Annual Report - New York State College of Home Economics, School of Education, Vice President for Research., 1959 (Box 31, Folder 22)
- Annual Report - Office of the Registrar., 1959 (Box 31, Folder 23)
- Annual Report - Graduate School of Nutrition., 1959 (Box 31, Folder 24)
- Annual Report - Vice President J. L. Zwingle, School of Hotel Administration, Dept. of Physical Education and Athletics, Graduate School of Business and Public Administration, College of Architecture., 1959 (Box 31, Folder 25)
- Annual Report - Summer Session., 1959 (Box 31, Folder 26)
- Annual Report - Cornell University Medical College, School of Nursing, College of Engineering, College of Arts and Sciences, Festival of Contemporary Arts., 1959 (Box 31, Folder 27)
- Annual Report - University Faculty, Division of Unclassified students, New York State Veterinary College., 1959 (Box 31, Folder 28)
- Annual Report - Veterinary Virus Research Institute, ROTC, New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations., 1959 (Box 31, Folder 29)
- Annual Report - Cornell University Library., 1959 (Box 31, Folder 30)
- Annual Report - Willard Straight Hall, Dept. of Physical Education and Athletics, Registrar, Social Science Research Center., 1960 (Box 31, Folder 31)
- Annual Report - Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory, College of Engineering., 1960 (Box 31, Folder 32)
- Annual Report - Cornell United Religious Work, School of Hotel Administration., 1960 (Box 31, Folder 33)
- Annual Report - Graduate School of Nutrition, Vice President J. L. Zwingle, Alumni Office, News Bureau, University Development, Graduate School., 1960 (Box 31, Folder 34)
- Annual Report - Dean of Students, School of Nursing, Cornell University Library., 1960 (Box 31, Folder 35)
- Annual Report - School of Education, New York State Veterinary College, Veterinary Virus Research Institute., 1960 (Box 31, Folder 36)
- Annual Report - Office of the Registrar, Festival of Contemporary Arts, Cornell University Medical College., 1960 (Box 31, Folder 37)
- Annual Report - College of Arts and Sciences, University Faculty, University Testing and Service Bureau, Summer Session, New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations., 1960 (Box 31, Folder 38)
- Annual Report - New York State College of Agriculture, University Placement Service, ROTC., 1960 (Box 31, Folder 39)
- Annual Report - ROTC, Cornell University Press, College of Architecture, Vice President for Research, New York State College of Home Economics., 1960 (Box 31, Folder 40)
- Annual Report - Dean of Students, New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations., 1961 (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Annual Report - New York State Veterinary College, New York State College of Agriculture, Social Science Research Center., 1961 (Box 32, Folder 2)
- Annual Report - Cornell University Library, New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations., 1961 (Box 32, Folder 3)
- Annual Report - New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations, Cornell United Religious Work, School of Hotel Administration, Admissions Office., 1961 (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Annual Report - Office of Admissions, Graduate School of Nutrition., 1961 (Box 32, Folder 5)
- Annual Report - Cornell University Medical College, College of Engineering., 1961 (Box 32, Folder 6)
- Annual Report - College of Engineering, New York State College of Home Economics., 1961 (Box 32, Folder 7)
- Annual Report - New York State College of Home Economics, Sage Infirmary and Clinic., 1961 (Box 32, Folder 8)
- Annual Report - Graduate School of Business and Public Administration, Cornell University Press., 1961 (Box 32, Folder 9)
- Annual Report - School of Education, University Placement Service., 1961 (Box 32, Folder 10)
- Annual Report - Willard Straight Hall, College of Arts and Sciences, Division of Unclassified Students., 1961 (Box 32, Folder 11)
- Annual Report - WHCU, Summer Session/ Graduate School, Willard Straight Hall., 1961 (Box 32, Folder 12)
- Annual Report - Willard Straight Hall, Social Science Research Center, Dept. of Physical Education and Athletics., 1961 (Box 32, Folder 13)
- Annual Report - University Faculty, School of nursing., 1961 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Annual Report - New York State Veterinary College, Vice President J. L. Zwingle, Alumni Office, News Bureau, Office of University Development., 1961 (Box 33, Folder 2)
- Annual Report - Dept. of Clinical and Preventive Medicine, ROTC, Secretary of the University, Festival of Contemporary Arts., 1961 (Box 33, Folder 3)
- Annual Report - New York State College of Agriculture., 1961 (Box 33, Folder 4)
- Annual Report - Vice President J. L. Zwingle / Office of University Development, University Relations Office/ News Bureau, Alumni Office., 1962 (Box 33, Folder 5)
- Annual Report - Graduate School of Nutrition, University Testing and Service Bureau, Willard Straight Hall, ROTC., 1962 (Box 33, Folder 6)
- Annual Report - News Bureau, Veterinary Virus Research Institute, College of Engineering, Cornell University Library., 1962 (Box 33, Folder 7)
- Annual Report - Law School, Cornell University Medical College, New York State Agricultural Experiment Station, School of Nursing., 1962 (Box 33, Folder 8)
- Annual Report - "An Introduction to Cornell,11 Sage Infirmary and Clinic, Graduate School, Graduate School of Business and Public Administration., 1962 (Box 33, Folder 9)
- Annual Report - New York State College of Home Economics., 1962 (Box 33, Folder 10)
- Annual Report - College of Architecture, College of Arts and Sciences, School of Education, School of Hotel Administration., 1962 (Box 33, Folder 11)
- Annual Report - Division of Unclassified Students, Cornell University Press, Cornell United Religious Work, University Placement Service., 1962 (Box 33, Folder 12)
- Annual Report - University Faculty, Dept. of Physical Education and Athletics, WHCU, Summer Session, Office of Admissions, Office of the Registrar., 1962 (Box 33, Folder 13)
- Annual Report - Office of the Registrar., 1962 (Box 33, Folder 14-15)
- "Stories from a twentieth-century Life", William Rees Sears, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Booklet: Charting the Second Century Under the Land-Grant Philosophy of Education, 1962 (Box 34, Folder 2)
- Cornell University Centennial Campaign, 1962 (Box 34, Folder 3)
- Cornell Alumni News: Centennial Convocation, 1964 (Box 34, Folder 4)
- IIE Seminar on Education in the Soviet Union Carnegie Endowment International Center, 1959 (Box 34, Folder 5)
- Annual Report: College of Engineering, 1961-1962 (Box 35, Folder 1)
- Annual Report: The Graduate School of Nutrition, 1961-1962 (Box 35, Folder 2)
- Annual Reports, 1961-1962 (Box 35, Folder 3-5)